<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!--
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2022 Felipe Kinoshita <kinofhek@gmail.com>
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  -->
  <id>org.kde.licentia</id>
  <name>Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">लाइसेंस</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">लाइसेंसिया</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Licentia</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxLicentiaxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Licentia</name>
  <summary>Choose a license for your project</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Trieu una llicència per al vostre projecte</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Seleccioneu una llicència per al vostre projecte</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zvolte si licenci pro svůj projekt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Wählen Sie eine Lizenz für Ihr Projekt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Choose a licence for your project</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Elektu permesilon por via projekto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Escoja una licencia para su proyecto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Aukeratu zure proiekturako lizentzia bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Valitse projektillesi lisenssi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Sélectionner une licence pour votre projet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Escolla unha licenza para un proxecto.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">בחירת רישיון למיזם שלך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">अपने प्रोजेक्ट के लिए लाइसेंस चुनें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Selige un licentia per tu projecto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Scegli una licenza per il tuo progetto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">აირჩიეთ თქვენი პროექტის ლიცენზია</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">내 프로젝트의 라이선스 선택</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Kies een licentie voor uw project</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wybierz licencję dla swojego projektu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Escolha uma licença para o seu projecto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">स्वस्य परियोजनायाः कृते अनुज्ञापत्रं चिनुत</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vyberte licenciu pre váš projekt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Izberite licenco za vaš projekt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Välj en licens för ditt projekt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Projeniz için bir lisans seçin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Виберіть умови ліцензування вашого проєкту</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxChoose a license for your projectxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">選擇適合您專案的授權條款</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer_name>KDE Community, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">La comunitat KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">La comunitat KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">KDE-Gemeinschaft, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Community, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eo">KDE-Komunumo, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">La Comunidad KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">KDE Komunitatea, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">KDE-yhteisö, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Communauté KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">Comunidade KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="he">קהילת KDE, פליפה קינושיטה</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hi">केडीई समुदाय, फेलिप किनोशिता</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ia">Communitate d KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Comunità KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ka">KDE-ის საზოგადოება, ფელიპე კინოშიტა</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">KDE 커뮤니티, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">KDE gemeenschap, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Społeczność KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Comunidade do KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sa">केडीई समुदाय, फेलिप किनोशिता</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">KDE komunita, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Skupnost KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">KDE Topluluğu, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE, Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Community, Felipe Kinoshitaxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE 社群、Felipe Kinoshita</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>Licentia helps you choose a license for your project, it allows you to check the license's permissions, conditions and limitations, how to add said license to your project and read the full license.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Licentia us ajuda a triar una llicència per al vostre projecte, permet comprovar els permisos, condicions i limitacions de la llicència, com afegir aquesta llicència al projecte i llegir la llicència completa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Licentia us ajuda a triar una llicència per al vostre projecte, permet comprovar els permisos, condicions i limitacions de la llicència, com afegir esta llicència al projecte i llegir la llicència completa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Licentia hilft Ihnen bei der Suche nach einer Lizenz für Ihr Projekt indem Sie die Berechtigungen, Konditionen und Einschränkungen überprüfen können, Informationen zum Hinzufügen der Lizenz gegeben werden und die vollständige Lizenz gelesen werden kann.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Licentia helps you choose a licence for your project, it allows you to check the licence's permissions, conditions and limitations, how to add said licence to your project and read the full licence.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Licentia helpas vin elekti permesilon por via projekto, ĝi permesas vin kontroli la permesojn, kondiĉojn kaj limigojn de la permesilo, kiel aldoni tiun permesilon al via projekto kaj legi la plenan permesilon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Licentia le ayuda a escoger una licencia para su proyecto. Le permite comprobar los permisos, las condiciones y las limitaciones de la licencia, cómo añadir dicha licencia a su proyecto y leer la totalidad de la licencia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«Licentia»k zure proiekturako lizentzia bat aukeratzen laguntzen dizu, lizentziaren baimenak, baldintzak eta mugak egiaztatzeko aukera ematen dizu, aipatutako lizentzia  zure proiektura nola gehitu eta lizentzia osoa nola irakurtzeko aukera ematen dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Licentia auttaa valitsemaan projektille lisenssin, tarkistamaan lisenssin oikeudet, käyttöehdot ja rajoitukset, ohjeistamaan miten lisätä lisenssi projektiin sekä lukemaan koko lisenssin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Licentia vous aide à sélectionner une licence pour votre projet. Ce logiciel vous permet de vérifier les autorisations, conditions et restrictions et vous indique comment ajouter la licence sélectionnée à votre projet et la lire en entier.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Licentia axúdalle a escoller unha licenza para un proxecto. Permítelle revisar os permisos, condicións e limitacións da licenza, así como as instrucións para engadir a licenza a un proxecto e ler a licenza completa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Licentia מסייעת לך לבחור רישיון למיזם שלך, היא מסייעת לך לבדוק מהן ההרשאות, התנאים והמגבלות של הרישיון, איך להוסיף רישיון מסוים למיזם שלך ולקרוא את הרישיון המלא.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">लाइसेंटिया आपको अपने प्रोजेक्ट के लिए लाइसेंस चुनने में मदद करता है, यह आपको लाइसेंस की अनुमतियों, शर्तों और सीमाओं की जांच करने, अपने प्रोजेक्ट में उक्त लाइसेंस को जोड़ने और पूर्ण लाइसेंस को पढ़ने की सुविधा देता है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Licentia te adjuta a seliger un licentia per tu projecto, illo te permitte verificar le permissiones, conditiones e restrictiones del licentia, como adder licentia dicite a tu projecto e lefer le plen licentia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Licentia ti aiuta a scegliere una licenza per il tuo progetto, ti permette di controllare i permessi, le condizioni e le limitazioni della licenza, come aggiungere detta licenza al tuo progetto e leggere la licenza completa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Licentia თქვენი პროექტისთვის ლიცენზიის არჩევაში დაგეხმარებათ. ის საშუალებას გაძლევთ, მონიშნოთ ლიცენზიის უფლებები, პირობები და შეზღუდვები, დაამატოთ არჩეული ლიცენზია თქვენს პროექტს და წაიკითხოთ სრული ლიცენზია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Licentia는 프로젝트의 라이선스 선택에 도움을 줍니다. 라이선스의 허가, 조건, 제약 사항을 확인할 수 있으며, 프로젝트에 라이선스를 적용하는 방법과 전체 라이선스를 안내합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Licentia helpt u bij het kiezen van een licentie voor uw project, het biedt u het controleren van de toestemmingen, bepalingen en beperkingen gegeven in de licentie, hoe de gekozen licentie aan uw project toevoegen en de volledige licentie te lezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Licentia pomaga wybrać licencję dla swojego projektu, pozwala sprawdzić uprawnienia, warunki i ograniczenia licencji, jak dodać daną licencję do swojego projektu oraz przeczytać pełną licencję.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Licentia ajuda-o a escolher uma licença para o seu projecto; permite-lhe verificar as permissões, condições e limitações, como adicionar a dita licença ao seu projecto e ler a licença completa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">Licentia भवतः परियोजनायाः कृते अनुज्ञापत्रं चयनं कर्तुं साहाय्यं करोति, एतत् भवन्तं अनुज्ञापत्रस्य अनुमतिः, शर्ताः, सीमाः च परीक्षितुं, उक्तं अनुज्ञापत्रं भवतः परियोजनायां कथं योजयितुं पूर्णं अनुज्ञापत्रं पठितुं च शक्नोति।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Licentia vam pomaga izbrati licenco za vaš projekt, omogoča preverjanje dovoljenj, pogojev in omejitev licence, kako dodati zahtevano licenco za vaš projekt in prebrati celotno licenco.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Licentia hjälper dig välja en licens för ditt projekt. Det låter dig kontrollera licensens rättigheter, villkor och begränsningar, hur nämnda licens kan läggas till i ditt projekt och läsa den fullständiga licensen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Licentia; projeniz için bir lisans seçmenize; lisansın izinlerini, koşullarını, sınırlandırmalarını denetlemenize; istenen lisansı projenize eklemenize ve tüm lisansı okumanıza izin verir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Licentia допоможе вибрати умови ліцензування для вашого проєкту. Програма надає вам змогу перевірити права доступу, умови та обмеження ліцензії, додати умови ліцензування до вашого проєкту та ознайомитися із повним текстом умов ліцензування.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxLicentia helps you choose a license for your project, it allows you to check the license's permissions, conditions and limitations, how to add said license to your project and read the full license.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Licentia 幫助您選擇專案的授權條款。其允許您檢查授權條款的權限、條件和限制，以及如何在您的專案聲明授權條款，和閱讀完整的授權條款內容。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/licentia/licentia.png</image>
      <caption>Main View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní pohled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Hauptansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Main View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefa Perspektivo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikuspegi nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Päänäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista principal.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגה ראשית</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">प्रमुख राय</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მთავარი ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">주 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok główny</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Janela Principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">मुख्य दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hlavný pohľad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavni pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudvy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ana Görünüm</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain Viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">主檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
  </recommends>
  <provides>
    <binary>licentia</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.licentia.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/fhek/licentia</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=Licentia&amp;component=general</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/community/donations/?app=org.kde.licentia</url>
</component>
